Guide to the Ellen Wallach and Thomas Darden, collectors, menu collection, 1937-1986.
Wallach, Ellen and Thomas Darden, collectors, menu collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ellen Wallach and Thomas Darden, collectors, menu collection, 1937-1986.
8526
Wallach, Ellen,
72 items
Menus.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Menus from various restaurants, predominately found out west.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Menus from various restaurants, predominately found out west.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wallach, Ellen,
Subjects:
Gastronomy.; Dinners and dining.; Restaurants.; Menus -- United States -- History -- 20th century
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Menus arranged alphabetically by state and city
- Hills Bros Coffee House, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Anaheim, California
  Notes: In Disneyland
- Steak House/Knott’s Berry Farm, 1956 (Box 1)
  Location: Buena Park, California
  Notes: Souvenir booklet
- Ghost town Grill/Knott’s Berry Farm, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: Child’s menu
- Silver Saddle Inn, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Downey, California
- The Brown Derby, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Los Angeles, California
- Casa La Golondrina, 1940s (Box 1)
- Don the Beachcomber, 1941 (Box 1)
  Location: Hollywood, California
  Notes: On Pacific Coast Highway- now closed
- Lawry’s - The Prime Rib, 1949 (Box 1)
  Notes: On La Cienega Blvd- Restaurant Row
- McHenry’s Tail O’ the Cock, October 30, 1937 (Box 1)
  Notes: Closed
- Richlor’s, 1948 (Box 1)
- Robb’s Century, 1961 (Box 1)
  Notes: 3 restaurants in LA
- Anthony’s Fish Grottos, 1972 (Box 1)
  Location: San Diego, California
  Notes: 3 restaurants
- John Tarantino’s Italian & Seafood, Undated (Box 1)
- Shelter Island Inn, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: Room service menu
- Ship Ashore Galley, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: Breakfast menu
- Tom Ham’s Lighthouse, Undated (Box 1)
- Barbary Coast, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: San Francisco, California
- George Mardikian, 1957 (Box 1)
- Sambo’s`, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Santa Barbara, California
  Notes: Sambo’s Games for Kids
- Kungsholm, 1949 (Box 1)
  Location: Chicago, Illinois
- Miller Bros., July 15, 1955 (Box 1)
  Location: Baltimore, Maryland
- Oyster Bar, Hotel Thunderbird, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Las Vegas, Nevada
- The Crystal Room, Desert Inn, 1971 (Box 1)
- Desert Inn & Country Club, 1971 (Box 1)
- Skillet Room, Desert Inn, 1971 (Box 1)
- Patio Cactus Room, Desert Inn, Undated (Box 1)
- Cactus Room, Desert Inn, 1971 (Box 1)
- Mr. Saturday’s Family Restaurant, Undated (Box 1)
- Union Plaza Hotel, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: 2 menus from the show, “Cabaret.”
- Pioneer Coffee Shop, Frontier Hotel, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: 2 menus
- Frontier Music Hall, Frontier Hotel, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: Advertising Jimmy Durante & Edie Adams show on the cover
- Frontier Steak House, Frontier Hotel, Undated (Box 1)
  Notes: 2 luncheon menus
- Cabaret, Frontier Hotel, Undated (Box 1)
- The Grand Cafe, June 26, 1950s (Box 1)
  Location: Reno, Nevada
  Notes: 2 menus- adult and child’s
- Brae Loch Inn, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Cazenovia, New York
  Notes: Hand written, closed
- Cadillac Restaurant, June 21, 1946 (Box 1)
  Location: New York City, New York
  Notes: “In the heart of Times Square” closed
- Space Needle Restaurant, 1960s (Box 1)
  Location: Seattle, Washington
  Notes: Souvenir menu
- Eddie Mays, 1950s (Box 1)
  Location: Oregon/Washington
  Notes: 22 restaurants
- Weller's Chalet Inn, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Washington
- Crab Broiler, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Seaside, Oregon
- Old Country Kitchen, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Portland, Oregon
  Notes: Menu a cut out of a steak
- Palaske’s Hillvilla, Undated (Box 1)
- Cross Roads Cafe, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Utah
  Notes: Blank menu, restaurant closed
- Sea Horse, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: USA
- Great Northern Railway, 1941 (Box 1)
  Location: Route of the Empire Builder
- S.S. Lurline, February 12-13, 1956 (Box 1)
  Location: San Francisco to Honolulu
  Notes: 2 ships menus
- T.S.S. Fairsea, 1982 (Box 1)
  Notes: Sitmar cruises- 10 menus
- ms Noordam, 1986 (Box 1)
  Notes: 86 Expo Cruise from Seattle to Vancouver
- Golden Dragon, 1950 (Box 1)
  Location: Burnaby, Canada
  Notes: Invitation to restaurant opening
- Copper Room, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Harrison Hot Springs, Canada
- Love’s, Undated (Box 1)
  Location: Vancouver, Canada
- Gaylord, Undated (Box 1)
- Hals, 1950s (Box 1)
  Location: Los Altos
- Harold’s Rose Room, Undated (Box 1)
- Cafe Monte Carlo, Undated (Box 1)